CORINNE JASKIEWICZ

ANALYST

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Experienced engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the environmental services industry. Strong mathematical background and proficiency in database software with a focus on analytics and visualizations. My goal is to create visually stimulating and understandable insight into analytical data.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JAVA R PYTHON SQL NoSQL TABLEAU FIGMA/ InVision HTML/ CSS

G SUITE MICRSOFT OFFICE SUITE

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

CREATIVITY COMMUNICATION COLLABORATION LEADERSHIP

INDEPENDENCE TIME MANAGEMENT ADAPTABILITY PROBLEM-SOLVING

MOTIVATION WORK ETHIC

EDUCATION

GRAND VALLEY STATE UNIVERSITY DATA SCIENCE AND ANALYTICS (M.S) 2018 - 2020

Graduated with a Professional Science Master's in Data Science and Analytics with top marks and a 3.95 GPA.

CORNELL UNIVERSITY ENVIRONMENTAL ENGINEERING (B.S) 2009 - 2013

Pursued Mechanical Engineering for two years, before to Environmental. Passed NCEES Engineer-in-Training exam prior to graduation.

WORK EXPERIENCE

GRADUATE ASSISTANT
GRAND VALLEY STATE UNIVERSITY
2018 - 2020

Acted as lead analyst for Graduate Exit Surveys administered through Qualtrics®. Reviewed website metrics through the CMS Platform.

BBJ GROUP, LLC STAFF ENGINEER, EIT 2014 - 2018

Acted as Staff Team Leader for the Compliance Team. Consistently worked on cross-departmental projects with efficiency and quality.